Guide to the Redtape Archive ca. 1972-1992 (Bulk 1982-1992) MSS.088
Fales Library and Special Collections
Redtape Archive
ca. 1972-1992
Fales Library and Special Collections
Redtape
MSS.088
3 Linear Feet in 4 boxes.
Redtape, edited and published by Michael Carter, was an East Village "zine" which throughout its run espoused innovative visual and literary expression while encouraging interplay between those two forms. The magazine, featuring comics, poetry, fiction, graphic art, and photography, provided a venue for both established and emerging writers and artists of the downtown scene. The collection includes a complete run of the magazine, mock-up copies and galleys, original art work, copies of art work, photographs, manuscripts and related correspondence, newspaper clippings, posters and flyers for readings, benefit parties and other events organized by Redtape participants.
Provenance
The Redtape Archive was acquired via purchase from its editor, Michael Carter in 1996. The collection was sorted by Marvin J. Taylor once it arrived at NYU. Archival materials were sorted into a series and processed later.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Historical Note:
Redtape, one of the East Village "zines", employing a magazine form to communicate innovative artistic ideas, divided its pages between literature and graphics, encouraging an interplay between writers and visual artists. According to the editor and publisher of Redtape Michael Carter the purpose of the magazine was "to explore new possibilities and forms of expression, to develop craft and technique without becoming sequestered in an intellectual or academic ivory tower". The magazine, featuring comics, poetry, fiction, graphic art, and photography, provided a venue for both established and emerging writers and artists of the downtown scene.
Intended initially as a quarterly publication, Redtape released seven issues in 10 years, each having a unique format and organized around specific theme: 'For the Left Side of Your Brain' (1982), 'Assemblage' (1982), 'Redtape: Double Summer Issue' (1983), 'ArtDamaged' (1984), 'White Lies' ( 1984), 'The Cracked Mirror' (1986) and 'Tragicomix' (1992). Issue No. 3 was the first time Carter consciously reached out to the art community. Since then, every issue expanded the list of contributors and the scope of the publication, making the magazine a part and product of the Lower East Side scene. From the fourth issue onwards, the magazine was published on glossy paper, capable of high-quality graphic reproduction.
Contributors to the magazine included Kathy Acker, Peter Chereches, Constance De Jong, John Farris, Richard Hambleton, Greer Lankton, Patrick McGrath, Lynne Tillman and David Wojnarowicz among many others.
Scope and Content Note
The collection includes a complete run of the magazine (including all variants), mock-up copies and gallows, original art work, copies of art work, photographs, manuscripts and related correspondence, newspaper clippings, ads, and posters and flyers for readings, benefit parties and other events organized by Redtape participants. The earliest materials submitted to the publication are dated 1972; however, the bulk of the material spans 1980-1992 (the period of the magazine's publication). The Collection contains many undated and/or unsigned documents, which, whenever possible, were identified using the published issues of the magazine and filed accordingly. Oversized archival materials from the various series are located in an oversize box at the end of the collection. All posters are located in the map case.
NOTE: Oversized material is in the numerical sequence of the series to which it belongs, though contained in separate boxes.
SERIES DESCRIPTIONS
Series I: Writings - contains poetry and fiction submitted for publication in Redtape. Materials are arranged alphabetically by author. Some folders include related correspondence.
Series II: Art/Comix - contains original artwork and photocopies. The original artwork consists of watercolors, drawings, graphic art, collages and transparencies. Some photocopies are signed and/or have handwritten titles. Whenever handwritten text on the photocopy was not intended as a part of the image, the work was considered a copy. However, if the image itself was modified in any way, the work was considered original. Subseries A contains the original work and subseries B contains copies
Series III: Photography - contains photographic prints submitted for publication in Redtape. Some of the photographs are original, while others reproduce the artwork present in the collection (Mike Cockrill)
Series IV: Production files - contains copies of magazine issues, drafts, mock-up copies and magazine page designs and layouts.
Series V: Events - contains ads, fliers and postcards announcing performances, art exhibits and readings by the authors, Redtape pre-publication celebrations and benefits parties.
Series VI: Miscellaneous - contains small-scale publications of Redtape contributors, 1 folder containing Michael Carter's incoming and outgoing correspondence relating to the magazine, and newspaper clippings of articles written by Michael Carter or mentioning Redtape magazine
Oversize: One flat oversize box at the end of the collection contains oversize materials from series 1, 2, 3, 4, and 5.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject/author heading.
The files are grouped into six subject-based series.
Series I: Correspondence
Series II: Art/Comix
Series III: Photography
Series IV: Production Files
Series V: Events
Series VI: Miscellaneous
Oversize - Series I: Correspondence
Oversize - Series II: Art/Comix
Oversize - Series III: Photography
Oversize - Series IV: Production Files
Oversize - Series V: Events
Oversize - Series VI: Miscellaneous
Related Material at the Fales Library and Special Collections
Ron Kolm Papers (MSS.079)
Tommy Turner Film Collection (MSS.099)
John Hall Papers (MSS.098)
Tim Dlugos Papers (MSS.087)
Between C& D Archive (MSS.084)
David Wojnarowicz Papers (MSS.092)
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
American literature -- 20th century.; Small presses -- New York (State) -- New York.; Magazines (Periodicals); Photographs.; Manuscripts for publication.; Authors, American -- 20th century.; Avant-garde (Aesthetics); Literature, Experimental.; Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.) -- Fiction.; Scripts (documents); Artists and community -- United States; New York (N.Y.) |v Fiction.; Posters.; American fiction -- 20th century.; New York (N.Y.).; New York (N.Y.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; Correspondence.; American fiction -- New York (State) -- New York.; Business records.; Fliers (printed matter); Comics (documents).; Tillman, Lynne; Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997; McGrath, Patrick, 1950-; Kolm, Ron; DeJong, Constance; Carter, Michael; Sanders, Ed; Wojnarowicz, David; Redtape
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Kathy Acker, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lester Afflick, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Daniel Aherne, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Neil Alers, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alfonso Akeela, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Richard Armijo, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Paul Barry, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Erica Baum, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - David Biddle, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Beth Biegler, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Star Black, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Max Blagg, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Les Bridges, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ronnie Burk, 1981 - 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Kathe Burkhart, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Steve Cannon, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Lawrence Caputo, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Michael Carter (aka Charles Perry?), 1982 - 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Peter Cherches, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bill Considine, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Robert Costa, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Eric Darton, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Simone Davis, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Constance DeJong, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Dana Delibovi, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Mark Dery, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Tom DeVenti, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Philip Dray, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Russell Epprecht, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Stacy Erra, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Maggie Estep, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - John Farris, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Jim Feast, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Orion Isaak Feig, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Cheryl Fish, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Dorothy Friedman, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Rachel Garmez, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Mike Golden, 1979 - 1989 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Joshua Golding, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Steve Greber, 1979 - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Jacek Gulla, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - John Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Robert Craig Hardin, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Christine Hatfull, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Barbara Holland, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Michael Horowitz, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - David Huberman, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Christian X. Hunter, 1990 - 1991 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Jennifer Kabat, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Kold, undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Ron Kolm, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Susan Kouguell, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Elmer Lang, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Lisa Lepore, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Sebastian Lockwood, undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Marian Lupo (aka Ravage), undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Ann Marlowe, undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Patrick McGrath, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Bernard Meisler, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Sharon Mesmer, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Raymond Metrulis, 1972 - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Larry Miller, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Stephen Miller, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Josheph Nechvatal, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Negro, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Sheryl Noethe, undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Michael O'Donoghue, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Mike Osterhorit, undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Eve Packer, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Jose Padua, undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Eddy Paris, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Allan Pearlman, undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Angela Perri, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Miguel Pi, undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Deborah Pintonelli, undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Wanda Phipps, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Bart Plantenga, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Victor Poison-T, undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Jonathan Prosser, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Michael Randal, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Jill Rappaport, undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - David Rattray, undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - John Read, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Joel Rose, undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Thadeus Rutkowski, 1984 - 1991 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Ari Salant, undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Ed Sanders, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Tom Savage, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Gail Shilke, undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Giulie Schuitzler, undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - JoAnn Schuman, undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Jonathan Seliger, undated (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Joe Semenovich, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Hal Sirowitz, undated (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Dr. Snakeskin (aka Darius James), undated (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Sparrow, undated (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Steven Taylor, undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Evie Teitlebaum, undated (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Fiona Templeton, undated (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Jack Thomas, undated (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Lynne Tillman, undated (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Kate Thompson, undated (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Jim Tobin, undated (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Mike Topp, undated (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Bill Trela, undated (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - David Ulin, undated (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - David Ulin & Steven Kane, undated (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Cecilia Vicu, undated (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Vindaloo, Z., undated (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Matthew Waldman, undated (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Diane Ward, undated (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Jennifer Waters, undated (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Carl Watson, undated (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Lauren Weber, undated (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Penelope Weholi, undated (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Enos Williams, undated (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Jeff Wright, undated (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Emily XYZ, undated (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Don Yorty, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Nina Zivancevic, undated (Box 1, Folder 126)
- Series II: Art/Comix
  - Subseries A: Original Art
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 15)
    - John Carey - 1 of 2, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - John Carey - 2 of 2, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Mike Cockrill - 1 of 4, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Mike Cockrill - 2 of 4, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Thom Corn, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - David Life, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - John Drury, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - John Ekhart, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Max Fish, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Geoff "Gizmo" Gilmore - "Insomnia Bar", undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Geoff "Gizmo" Gilmore - "Mars Bar", 1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Gustav Hagglund, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Richard Hofman, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Patrick Howe - 1 of 7, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Patrick Howe - 2 of 7, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Patrick Howe - 3 of 7, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Patrick Howe - 4 of 7, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Patrick Howe - 5 of 7, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Christof Kohlhofer, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Milton Knight Jr., undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - D. L., undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Neil Martinson, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Tom Marsan, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Tom McGlynn, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Taylor Mead, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Kembra Pfahler - 1 of 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Tim Ray, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Michael Roman - 1 of 5, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Leslie Rowe, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Shalom, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Siobhan, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Leslie Sternbergh, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Daryl Trivieri, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Kevin Wendall (aka Fa-Q), undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - David West, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Subseries B: Copy
    - Richard Armijo, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Jane Baumer, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Fred Bertucci, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Edward Brezinski, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Stacie J. Brown, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Jonh Carey, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Michael Carter, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Steve Cerio, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Bob Cook - 1 of 2, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Bob Cook/Jack David, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Scott Cunningham, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Eric Drooker, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Jennifer ExBowen, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Gustav Hagglund - "The Agony of Marble Bones", undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Gustav Hagglund - "Oracle Bones", undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Gustav Hagglund - "Cop Shot Dream", undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Gustav Hagglund - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Richard Hambleton, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Danny Hellman - 1 of 2, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Pamela Hobbs, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Partick Howe, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Krystyna Jachniewicz, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Michael Kupperman, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Andrew Listfield, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Tom Marsan, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Arnold Mesches, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Tony Millioaire/Julius Klein, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Gary Panter, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Robert Petrick, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Rick Prol, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - James Romberger / David Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Salon Bon Ton, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - David Sandlin, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Lorraine Schein, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Shalom, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Siobhan, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Walter Sipster, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Art Spiegelman, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Mick Stern, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Jim Tobin, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Chumley Twist/Anne Autre, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Mick Zedd, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Series III: Photography
  - Unidentified photographs, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Gary Azon, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Alan Belcher, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Jim C. - negative of Edward Brezinski's "Bianca Jagger", undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Jim C., undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Michael Carter - Photo of David Wojnarovicz, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mike Cockrill - 1of 3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Mike Cockrill - 2of 3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Mike Cockrill - 3of 3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Tom Cott - "White Lies", undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ivan Dalla Tana, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Efraim Gonzalez - 1 of 2, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Efraim Gonzalez - 2 of 2, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Richard Hambleton, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Richard Hambleton "Sunset", 1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Jim Kellough - 1 of 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Jim Kellough - 2 of 2, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Greer Lankton - 1 of 7, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Greer Lankton - 2 of 7, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Greer Lankton - 3 of 7, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Greer Lankton - 4 of 7, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Greer Lankton - 5 of 7, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Greer Lankton - 6 of 7, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Greer Lankton - 7 of 7, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Tina Paul, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Pelka/Noble Photography - Gretchen Bender, "Untitled", undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Franc Plaia, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Marie Ruggirello, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Marion S. - 1 of 3, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Marion S. - 2 of 3, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Marion S. - 3 of 3, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Walter Sipster, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Andreas Sterzing, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Susan Strande, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Toyo - "from Bill Considine's Electra", undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Toyo - Kembra Phahler, "Murder Mysteries" - 1 of 2, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Toyo - Kembra Phahler, "Murder Mysteries" - 1 of 2, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Toyo - Richard Armjo - untitled, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Toyo -Painting by Jed Jackson, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Toyo - Painting by Nadia Coen - 1 of 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Toyo - Painting by Nadia Coen - 2 of 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Toyo - Triptych - 1 of 3, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Toyo - Triptych - 2 of 3, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Toyo - Triptych - 3 of 3, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Toyo - Untitled, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Tom Warren - 1 of 4, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Tom Warren - 2 of 4, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Tom Warren - 3 of 4, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Tom Warren - 4 of 4, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - David Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Kryzysztof Zarebski - 1 of 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Kryzysztof Zarebski - 1 of 2, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Series IV: Production Files
  - Redtape 1 - 2 copies, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Redtape 1 - General, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Redtape 2 - 1 copy, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Redtape 3 - 2 copies, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Redtape 3 - General, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Redtape 4 - 1 copy (cmp w/real), undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Redtape 4 - General, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Redtape 5 - 3 copies without covers, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Redtape 5 - General, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Redtape 5 - Pre-publication edition, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Redtape 7 - Mock-up copy, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Series V: Events
  - Redtape 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Redtape 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Redtape 3, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Redtape 4, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Redtape 5, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Redtape 7, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Series VI: Miscellaneous
  - Michael Carter - miscellaneous, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ron English, Art is a Horrible Waste of Imagination, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Danny Hellman/Geoff Gilmore, Coffee Drinkin' Man, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Pinched Nerves, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Pink Tape, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Smirk, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Tom Warren - postcard, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Photo of David Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - David Wojnarowicz, In the Shadow of Forward Motion, notes by Felix Guattari, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Oversize - Series I: Correspondence
  - Holly Anderson (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Don Deering (Oversized), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Norman Douglas (Oversized), undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Dumas (Oversized), undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - David Wojnarowicz (Oversized), undated (Box 3, Folder 115)
- Oversize - Series II: Art/Comix
  - Subseries A: Original Art
    - Ads - Danceteria (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Richard Armijo (Oversized), undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Jane Bauman - 1 of 2 (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Jane Bauman, 1984 (Folder 17)
    - Brezinski, undated (Folder 17)
    - Mike Cockrill - 3 of 4 (Oversized+, very fragile), undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Mike Cockrill - 4 of 4 (Oversized+, very fragile), undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Linus Corragio - 1 of 2 (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Linus Corragio - 2 of 2 (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Daze (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Richard Hofman (Oversized), undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Patrick Howe - 6 of 7 (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Patrick Howe - 7 of 7 (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - James (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Tom Marsan / Nick D. (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Mitti Masden (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Joseph Nechvatal (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Paulette Nenner "Underwolf" (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Kembra Pfahler - 2 of 2 (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Michael Rheingold - Sofas (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Michael Rheingold - Dogs (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Michael Roman - 2 of 5(Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Michael Roman - 3 of 5 (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Michael Roman - 4 of 5 (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Michael Roman - 5 of 5 (Oversized++), undated (Folder 16)
    - John Rosis "Clown Control" (Oversized +), undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Leslie Rowe (Oversized +), undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Lorie Sheridan (Oversized+), undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Walter Sipster (Oversized +), undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - John Terhorst (Oversized +), undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Seth Tobolman (Oversized), undated (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Conrad Vogel (Oversized), undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Oversize - Subseries B: Copy
    - Scot Borofsky (Oversized+), undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bob Cook - 2 of 2 (Oversized), undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Mike Diana (Oversize ?), undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Cheryl Dyer (Oversized+), undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Danny Hellman - 2 of 2 (Oversized), undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Julius Klein (Oversized +), undated (Box 4, Folder 28)